We're we're deep in 2024 right now and I
actually just sat down with my team. We
were going through um our production
planning and just just looking at how we
far we've come and how in integral
fulfill has been to it. I mean there's
no way we could be having this
conversation right now. We would be just
dead in the water. fulfill has really
changed our business um when it comes to
managing our stock and our inventory and
and on the back of that being able to do
really strong demand planning and it's
funny because I was hearing about uh in
chat another vendor of uh inventory
management software and uh we actually
onboarded that vendor like the day I
started at Hexcloud in early 2020. 20
and we never went live with it. It was
that bad. So you can make really really
bad decisions in this area. You can
literally b burn tens of thousands of
dollars and not have it work, not have
it even ever go live. And we implemented
fulfill uh at a key time in 2023 and uh
Q4 was a monster for us and we wouldn't
have done it uh nearly as well without
fulfill and this 2024 planning that
we're finalizing now our production
planning like I just don't know where we
would be without it. Well, Jason, I'll
go ahead and say someone in in chat is
trying to set up Netswuite, and they
said, "Hey, we got quoted uh 12 months
and like $250,000 in setup costs." And
no software on earth should ever take
that long to set up. I would literally
rather quit this industry and go be, I
don't know, a farmer. Yeah. Barista,
then spend 12 months in software. So
fulfills promise is it won't take 12
months. Uh and Jason's using it right
now to plan 2024. And Jason, just quick
ballpark. You think it's going to be
three or four billion this year in
sales? Is that what you're planning?
>> No, but we're going for
like high double digit growth this year.
So, another huge year in the Hexclad
family powered by Fulfill.